(Sheldon:)this is a thermostat.
(Sheldon:)It controls the temperature
of the apartment.
(Sheldon:)The ideal setting is 72 degrees.
(Sheldon:)If you find this too cold,
then put on a jacket.
(Sheldon:)A straitjacket, 'cause 72's
the best and you're crazy.
(Sheldon:)Now... this...
(Sheldon:)is your spot.
(Sheldon:)You're very protective of it.
(Sheldon:)When anyone else tries
to sit here,
(Sheldon:)you berate them relentlessly.
(Sheldon:)It sounds mean, but
somehow you make it adorable.
(Sheldon:)People are also delighted
by your love of pranks.
(quietly):
For example, Leonard has no idea
(Sheldon:)what I did to his coffee.
It wasn't "replace it
with Folger's crystals,"
(Sheldon:)I'll tell you that much.
(Leonard:)Hey, can we please
get back to work?
(Sheldon:)This is Leonard.
(Sheldon:)He's your best friend
in the world.
(Leonard:)All right, just stop.
This is ridiculous.
(Sheldon:)Sometimes he gets cranky,